[
    {
        "title": "Maybe!"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "USA invaded Afghanistan, Harry Potter and The Sorcerer’s Stone was the top film, The Office started on TV",
        "answer": "2001"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Novak Djokovic was deported from Australia, The Gray Report was published, A drought is declared in large parts of England",
        "answer": "2022"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Gordon Brown was Prime Minister, Sully crash landed an airliner in the Hudson River, Michael Jackson died",
        "answer": "2009"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Sir Elton John announces that he is to retire from touring after nearly fifty years, Harry Kane scored a hat-trick as England beat Panama 6-1, Chas from Chas and Dave died",
        "answer": "2018"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The Wheel, hosted by Michael McIntyre, debuted on BBC 1, The Weeknd had a hit with Blinding Lights, Protests took place across the UK after the murder of George Floyd",
        "answer": "2020"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Golfer Danny Willett won the US Masters, Andy Murray reaches number one in the world tennis rankings, Leicester City won the Premier League for the first time",
        "answer": "2016"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Ellen MacArthur sailed solo around the world, The Prince of Wales married Camilla Parker Bowles, The Hunting Act banned hunting with dogs in England and Wales",
        "answer": "2005"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "HMV goes into administration, Oscar Pistorius murdered his girlfriend Reeva Steenkamp, Bedroom tax was introduced by the coalition government",
        "answer": "2013"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "The half crown ceases to be legal tender, Black Sabbath release their debut album, Martin Peters became the first player to be transferred for £200,000",
        "answer": "1970"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Jude Bellingham was born, Maurice Gibb died, The rebuilt Bull Ring shopping centre in Birmingham is officially opened",
        "answer": "2003"
    }
]
